import { Injectable } from '@angular/core';

@Injectable()
export class DataService {

  constructor() { }

  storage=[
    {
      username: 'user1',
      email: 'user1@cts.com',
      secretQuestion: 'What is your pet name?',
      answer: 'usrone',
      gender: 'male'
    },
    {
      username: 'user2',
      email: 'user2@cts.com',
      secretQuestion: 'What is your pet name?',
      answer: 'usrtwo',
      gender: 'female'
    },
    {
      username: 'user3',
      email: 'user3@cts.com',
      secretQuestion: 'What is your pet name?',
      answer: 'usrthree',
      gender: 'male'
    },
    {
      username: 'user4',
      email: 'user4@cts.com',
      secretQuestion: 'What is your pet name?',
      answer: 'usrfour',
      gender: 'female'
    },
    {
      username: 'user5',
      email: 'user5@cts.com',
      secretQuestion: 'What is your pet name?',
      answer: 'usrfive',
      gender: 'male'
    },
    {
      username: 'user6',
      email: 'user6@cts.com',
      secretQuestion: 'What is your pet name?',
      answer: 'usrsix',
      gender: 'female'
    },
    {
      username: 'user7',
      email: 'user7@cts.com',
      secretQuestion: 'What is your pet name?',
      answer: 'usrseven',
      gender: 'male'
    },
    {
      username: 'user8',
      email: 'user8@cts.com',
      secretQuestion: 'What is your pet name?',
      answer: 'usreight',
      gender: 'female'
    },
    {
      username: 'user9',
      email: 'user9@cts.com',
      secretQuestion: 'What is your pet name?',
      answer: 'usrnine',
      gender: 'male'
    },
    {
      username: 'user10',
      email: 'user10@cts.com',
      secretQuestion: 'What is your pet name?',
      answer: 'usrten',
      gender: 'female'
    }    
  ];

}
